<resources>
    <string name="app_name">STEMify</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string name="health_lifestyle">Embracing a healthy lifestyle involves eating well, staying active, and taking care of your mental well-being.</string>

    <string name="health_1">A healthy diet
        \nA healthy diet involves eating a variety of foods in the correct proportions and consuming a calorie intake that allows for the maintenance of healthy body weight. Although this varies for everyone,
        as a general guide, this should include:
    \n\n\ta. Five portions of fruit and vegetables per day
    \n\tb. Lean proteins, especially fish, eggs, and white meat, are essential for cellular repair and provide a range of vitamins and minerals
    \n\tc. Dairy foods and their alternatives, which are a good source of protein and provide calcium.
    \n\td. Starchy foods, particularly wholegrain varieties which contain more fiber and nutrients
    \n\te. Limited amounts of unsaturated fats.
    </string>

    <string name="health_2">Physical activity
    \nThe World Health Organisation recommends that all adults undertake regular physical activity, including at least thirty minutes of moderate aerobic activity daily, supplemented by at least two weight-bearing activity sessions per week.
    \n</string>

    <string name="health_3">Sleep
    \nTry to get 7-8 hours every night and try to keep a regular sleep-wake cycle – go to bed and get up at the same time every day. A good nights sleep may make you more productive and efficient on the next day.\n </string>

    <string name="health_4">Drink Plenty of Water
    \nOur body is 75% water and it is necessary to maintain the amount of liquid we consume, especially water as it is the most vital liquid humans require. 8 glasses a day also equal to 3 litres of water a day should keep you
    hydrated and healthy. \n</string>

    <string name="health_5">Socialise
    \nHaving a healthy diet and exercising aren\'t the only contributors in having a healthy lifestyle, socialise with your peers and have some fun once in a while to keep yourself
    (mind and body) healthy and free of stress\n</string>

    <string name="mental_main">Mental health is crucial, but what about understanding the science behind it? Unravel the brain\'s adaptability with neuroplasticity, uncover the neurotransmitters that sway emotions, and understand your
        stress response system. Get set to dive deep into the fascinating science that underpins mental health!</string>

    <string name="mental_1">Think of your brain as a flexible gym for mental fitness! Neuroplasticity highlights your brain\'s ability to adapt and grow, shaping how you learn and cope with challenges. Its the secret ingredient behind building resilience and positive mental habits.</string>
    <string name="mental_2">Imagine your brain as a chemical orchestra! Serotonin, dopamine, and other neurotransmitters dictate your mood, motivation, and stress responses. They\'re the conductors ensuring your brain\'s performance stays in harmony.</string>
    <string name="mental_3">Your brain, the superhero managing stress! The amygdala acts like a vigilant guard, orchestrating your body\'s fight-or-flight response. Its your brain\'s way of preparing you for action in demanding situations.</string>
    <string name="mental_4">Picture your brain and body as dance partners! Your thoughts and emotions have a direct impact on your physical well-being, showcasing the strong link between mental health and overall health. It\'s a seamless coordination for your overall wellness!</string>
    <string name="mental_5">Help free yourself of constantly swirling thoughts by reconnecting yourself with where you are at this moment in time. Follow along with the video below or simply take three slow deep breaths, feel your feet grounded on the floor</string>

    <string name="clean_main">Many people equate hygiene with "cleanliness", but hygiene is a broad term. It includes such personal habit choices as how frequently to take a shower or bath, wash hands, trim fingernails, and wash clothes. It also includes attention to keeping surfaces in the home and workplace clean, including bathroom facilities.\n
    So, when did it all start?</string>

    <string name="clean_wash">The history of hygiene spans civilizations, evolving from early practices like ancient bathing rituals to the modern understanding of germ theory, prompting advancements in sanitation, clean water access, and public health measures.</string>

    <string name="clean_germs">The exploration of pivotal scientific moments in cleanliness history involves significant milestones, such as the discovery of bacteria by Antonie van Leeuwenhoek in the 17th century, revolutionizing our understanding of hygiene and prompting advancements in public health measures.</string>

    <string name="clean_micro">Microbes are like the superheroes and villains of our body—they help with digestion but can also cause diseases. Learning about them is like uncovering a tiny, invisible world that impacts our health!</string>

    <string name="clean_micro2">The exploration of the human microbiome, the vast community of microbes living in and on our bodies, has been a recent focus. This area of research has unveiled surprising connections between microbial communities and our health, influencing everything from our immune system to mental well-being.
        \n\nUnderstanding the microbial world has transformed hygiene practices. From the development of effective antibiotics to the implementation of stringent sterilization techniques, STEM-driven innovations have significantly improved sanitation standards, minimizing the risk of infectious diseases.</string>

   <string name="clean_practice">Now that we know more about hygiene, how do we practice living a clean and hygienic lifestyle?\nIts easy, make sure
   to always take care of your personal hygiene by washing your wash every morning and evening, brushing your teeth for at least 3 times a day and taking a bath for a minimum
   of 2 times a day. Always remember to wash your hands and feet to prevent the unwanted microorganisms entering your body.</string>

    <string name="clean_future">In the world of tomorrow, cleanliness is taking on a whole new dimension. Picture this: cleaning robots zipping around using UV-C rays to zap germs out of existence, smart toilets analyzing health data, and surfaces that stay spotless, all thanks to innovative technology. But it is not just about being tidy; it is
        about being eco-smart too! The future of cleanliness embraces sustainability with biodegradable products and zero-waste practices. And lets not forget the personalized touch – from skincare customized for your skin type to hygiene routines tailored to your needs, cleanliness in the future is all about personalized, tech-savvy, and eco-friendly approaches.</string>

    <string name="fit_main">Explore the captivating biology behind health and fitness, delving into how our bodies function during exercise, recover, and adapt. Uncover the intricate interplay of muscles, metabolism, and endurance that empowers us in our pursuit of a healthier lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="fit_cardio">Picture your heart as a champion athlete! Through regular exercise, it pumps more efficiently, just like a supercharged engine, delivering oxygen and nutrients to your muscles faster. Its like your heart upgrading to a turbo mode!</string>

    <string name="fit_yoga">Your brain becomes a happy factory during exercise! It releases mood-lifting chemicals called endorphins, making you feel like you have just had a dose of joy. Its like a dance party for your brain cells!</string>
    <string name="fit_muscle">Think of muscles as adaptable superheroes! When you exercise, they respond by repairing and growing stronger. Imagine them like construction workers building a fortress; each workout adds more strength and resilience</string>
    <string name="fit_rest">Your body becomes a metabolic magician during workouts! It shifts gears between different energy systems, burning calories like a furnace and giving you that energized feeling. Think of it as your body\'s power-up mode, turning you into a calorie-burning superhero!</string>

    <string name="event1">The World Health Assembly is the decision-making body of WHO. It is attended by delegations from all WHO Member States and focuses on a specific health agenda to notify all the citizens on the World Health Association and the upcoming projects. People from all around the world are invited to join the assembly</string>
    <string name="event2">Come join us in investigating the science behind mental health and how it is transmitted in the brain. With a group of talented professors from University Sabah Malaysia, watch us unfold how the brain and mental health are interrelated. Free admission so save the date and join!</string>
    <string name="event3">Technology and Wellness are about to reach great lengths, join TechCares as they share how technology can positively impact the environment in ensuring a healthy life for the future generations. With insights and lucky draw sessions in the end, this forum is going to be on of the best yet!</string>
    <string-array name="materialType">
        <item>Type of material</item>
        <item>Video Lesson</item>
        <item>Practice</item>
        <item>Quiz</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="durationQuiz">
        <item>5</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>15</item>
        <item>20</item>
        <item>25</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>35</item>
        <item>40</item>
        <item>45</item>
        <item>50</item>
        <item>55</item>
        <item>60</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="questionType">
        <item>Multiple-question</item>
        <item>Fill-in-the-blank</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="doctor">"Doctors, also known as physicians, are licensed health professionals who maintain and restore human health through the practice of medicine. They examine patients, review their medical history, diagnose illnesses or injuries, administer treatment, and counsel patients on their health and well-being."</string>
    <string name="chemist">"A chemist is a scientist who performs research and experiments related to chemistry. They help to develop products like vaccinations and medications and analyze them to determine their composition, concentration and safety. They prepare technical reports to describe the methods and results of their research."</string>
    <string name="software_engineer">"A Software Engineer, or Software Development Engineer, is responsible for developing software programs or systems that align with user needs. Their duties include meeting with clients or business professionals to strategize ideas for beneficial software, coordinating with other IT professionals to design software and running tests to catch coding errors."</string>
    <string name="web_developer">"A web developer designs and programs websites, typically either on the front-end or back-end of production. Web developers code web pages and work on the interactivity and visual effects used in websites. They also analyze user needs, test the websites they develop and collect user feedback to improve the functionality of web pages."</string>
    <string name="computer_system_analyst">"A computer systems analyst helps companies improve their computer systems, resolve information technology-related issues, suggest enhancements and ensure their technology is up-to-date. A computer systems analyst might work on improving communication and security. They may also install new systems and programs and implement customized solutions based on the company's requirements."</string>
    <string name="cost_estimator">"A cost estimator analyzes data to determine the amount of money, materials, labor and time it takes to complete projects. Cost estimators try to ensure that projects stay within an established budget and that they're completed on time. They also manage bid pricing from vendors, prepare detailed cost analyses, discuss their estimates with team members and trade partners and establish and maintain relationships with vendors and subcontractors."</string>
    <string name="industrial_engineer">"An industrial engineer creates systems to help maximize the efficiency and productivity of manufacturing companies or service providers. They also try to reduce waste during the completion of projects and improve current processes. They may develop and implement quality control and cost-saving measures and standardize and optimize systems to distribute goods and services more efficiently."</string>
    <string name="civil_engineer">"A civil engineer works on construction projects such as roads or bridges. Their job involves designing, building and repairing large structures. They may specialize in a particular field, such as architectural, construction or transportation engineering."</string>
    <string name="mechanical_engineer">"A mechanical engineer works in a variety of industries and designs, creates and tests machines or mechanical devices. They can also repair machines like refrigerators, elevators and combustion engines. They play a crucial role in transforming an idea or plan into a product."</string>
    <string name="statistician">"A statistician collects and analyzes data and uses the results to help companies and organizations maximize their profits and minimize risk. They use the data they collect to inform business and investment decisions and identify trends in global markets and in different job fields. They help companies make reasonable conclusions using the results of their previous data analysis."</string>
    <string name="khazanah">"Offered by the Yayasan Khazanah foundation, this scholarship program is open to all Malaysian citizens. This government initiative provides fully-funded awards to students in fields like business, engineering, life sciences, and other fields necessary to Malaysia’s development. If you’re eligible, you receive complete financial support, covering fees, living costs, accommodation and more."</string>
    <string name="mybrainsc">"This is an initiative by the Malaysian Ministry of Education to raise a generation of young scientists and scholars. The program covers scholarship for Malaysian students at undergraduate and postgraduate levels enrolled in natural science programs. Scholarships for Malaysian students studying abroad are open for top globally ranked universities in the Australia, US, Canada, and UK. The award covers expenses including tuition fees, living costs, accommodation, and things like your flight tickets, visa-related fees and so on. After completing your studies you agree to return to Malaysia and work in a government-approved school or research institution."</string>
    <string name="bank_negara">"Bank Negara Malaysia offers full scholarships for Malaysian students abroad and at home, at pre-university, undergraduate and graduate levels. The award programs cover study in commerce, math and computer science fields."</string>
    <string name="jpa">"This government-provided scholarship funds foundational and undergraduate studies in Japan, Korea, France, and Germany. The fields funding is available to cover engineering, science, technology, and social sciences. This is a loan offered by the government to SPM students. You need to enrol in preparatory courses at a local school before attending a university in one of the 4 countries above."</string>
    <string name="fullbright">"This is a US-government program in partnership with 160 countries. Fullbright offers partial grants to Malaysian citizens for postgraduate study in the US. This means the grant supplements your personal funds and any existing scholarships or other funding you receive. The amount of the grant varies depending on the funding already available to you. So, this scholarship is a great option if you scored a partial scholarships from a home institution or the university you’ll be studying at."</string>
    <string name="british_council">"GREAT Scholarships is a partner program between the UK government and the British Council. A total of 30 scholarships across many different fields are on offer for postgraduate study. The scholarship amounts to £10,000 to cover tuition for a one-year postgraduate course at a UK university."</string>
</resources>