<resources>
    <string name="app_name">STEMify</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string name="health_lifestyle">Embracing a healthy lifestyle involves eating well, staying active, and taking care of your mental well-being.</string>

    <string name="health_1">A healthy diet
        \nA healthy diet involves eating a variety of foods in the correct proportions and consuming a calorie intake that allows for the maintenance of healthy body weight. Although this varies for everyone,
        as a general guide, this should include:
    \n\n\ta. Five portions of fruit and vegetables per day
    \n\tb. Lean proteins, especially fish, eggs, and white meat, are essential for cellular repair and provide a range of vitamins and minerals
    \n\tc. Dairy foods and their alternatives, which are a good source of protein and provide calcium.
    \n\td. Starchy foods, particularly wholegrain varieties which contain more fiber and nutrients
    \n\te. Limited amounts of unsaturated fats.
    </string>

    <string name="health_2">Physical activity
    \nThe World Health Organisation recommends that all adults undertake regular physical activity, including at least thirty minutes of moderate aerobic activity daily, supplemented by at least two weight-bearing activity sessions per week.
    \n</string>

    <string name="health_3">Sleep
    \nTry to get 7-8 hours every night and try to keep a regular sleep-wake cycle – go to bed and get up at the same time every day. A good nights sleep may make you more productive and efficient on the next day.\n </string>

    <string name="health_4">Drink Plenty of Water
    \nOur body is 75% water and it is necessary to maintain the amount of liquid we consume, especially water as it is the most vital liquid humans require. 8 glasses a day also equal to 3 litres of water a day should keep you
    hydrated and healthy. \n</string>

    <string name="health_5">Socialise
    \nHaving a healthy diet and exercising aren\'t the only contributors in having a healthy lifestyle, socialise with your peers and have some fun once in a while to keep yourself
    (mind and body) healthy and free of stress\n</string>

    <string name="mental_main"> It is understandable to feel scared, anxious or helpless during this
        unprecedented time. But whatever situation you are in and wherever you are in the World,
        you have the power to look after your mental health and well-being.</string>

    <string name="mental_1">Amidst the whirlwind of academics and social engagements, remember to prioritize self-care. This includes nourishing your body with proper nutrition, getting adequate sleep, and engaging in physical activity.
        Taking care of yourself physically can profoundly impact your mental health. Small acts of self-care can make a big difference in how you feel every day.</string>

    <string name="mental_2">It’s okay to feel down sometimes. Life has its highs and lows, and experiencing a range of emotions is entirely normal. Don’t be too hard on yourself for feeling sad, anxious, or stressed. Acknowledging these
        emotions and allowing yourself to feel them is an essential part of coping and healing. Remember, it’s okay not to be okay sometimes.</string>

    <string name="mental_3">Try to continue doing the activities that you find meaningful and enjoyable, such as cooking for yourself or your loved ones, playing with your pet, walking in the park, reading a book, or watching a film or TV series.
        Having a regular routine with activities that make you feel happy will help you maintain good mental health.</string>

    <string name="mental_4">You\'re not alone in this journey. Having a support network can make a world of difference. Whether it\'s friends, family, teachers, or counselors, having someone to confide in can provide comfort and guidance during tough
        times. Don’t hesitate to seek help when you need it. Support is crucial for maintaining good mental health.</string>

    <string name="mental_5">Help free yourself of constantly swirling thoughts by reconnecting yourself with where you are at this moment in time. Follow along with the video below or simply take three slow deep breaths, feel your feet grounded on the floor</string>

    <string name="clean_main">Cleanliness is the most important habit one can possess, as cleanliness and health are interrelated.\n
    So how to keep it clean? </string>

    <string name="clean_wash">Your hands may look clean but doesn’t necessarily mean they are. Wash hand properly and thoroughly with soap and water</string>

    <string name="clean_bath">Showering twice a day in the ideal way to keep our bodies clean and hygiene. Not only does it keep our body clean, it also makes us feel clean and more comfortable. It is important to make sure to clean your entire body in the shower.\n
    Showering 5-10 minutes a day is a suitable amount of time for soaping up and rinsing off. Keeping our bodies clean ultimately help us to be more healthy! </string>

    <string name="clean_teeth">Taking care of your teeth and gums is vital for good oral health, especially in areas with limited resources. Brushing teeth twice daily with fluoride toothpaste, using traditional methods like chewing sticks or neem twigs, and visiting
        a local dental worker can help prevent tooth decay and gum disease.\nRegular care ensures healthier smiles and reduces dental issues even in areas with fewer resources.</string>

    <string name="clean_cloth">It\'s recommended to wash clothes regularly, especially undergarments and those worn close to the skin, after each use or every few wears, depending on the level of activity and sweat. Airing clothes in the sun also helps reduce odors and keeps clothes clean.\n
    Regular washing is crucial as it prevents skin infections, improves personal hygiene and makes life healthier and more comfortable.</string>

    <string name="fit_main">Explore the benefits of exercising outdoors, enhancing brain health through meditation, and making small yet impactful exercise choices. Remember, a balanced routine is key to a healthier mind and body</string>

    <string name="fit_hiking">Who needs a gym membership when you have the outdoors?\n
	Outdoor exercise has a stronger effect on blood pressure and mood than indoor exercise. Stress is relieved within minutes of exposure to nature as measured by muscle tension, blood pressure, and brain activity.\
        To put it simply, time spent outside is good for you!</string>

    <string name="fit_yoga">With your eyes closed, simply breathe in while saying "breathe in" in your head as you do. Then breathe out and say "breathe out". For the next 20 minutes or so, your aim is to focus on this circular breath and the simple words in your head as much as possible.\n
	Focusing on your brain health is one of the best things you can do to improve your concentration, focus, memory, and mental agility, no matter what age you are.</string>

    <string name="fit_squat">When you\'re feeling too lazy and tired to exercise, these are some activities you can follow that can help.\nSquatting and stretching!\n
    Squats burn calories and might help you lose weight. They also lower your chances of injuring your knees and ankles.\nStretching keeps your muscles flexible, strong and healthy, and we need that flexibility to maintain a range of motion in the joints. </string>

    <string name="fit_rest">Sometimes all you need is a good lazy day where you do not make your muscles and body more tired. Taking rest days can improve sleep, much like regular exercises. Moreover, lack of sleep may result in low motivation to take part in leisure activities. Always have a good balance in keeping your body and mind fit. </string>

    <string name="event1">The World Health Assembly is the decision-making body of WHO. It is attended by delegations from all WHO Member States and focuses on a specific health agenda to notify all the citizens on the World Health Association and the upcoming projects. People from all around the world are invited to join the assembly</string>
    <string name="event2">Come join us in investigating the science behind mental health and how it is transmitted in the brain. With a group of talented professors from San Jose, watch us unfold how the brain and mental health are interrelated. Free admission so save the date and join!</string>
    <string name="event3">Technology and Wellness are about to reach great lengths, join TechCares as they share how technology can positively impact the environment in ensuring a healthy life for the future generations. With insights and lucky draw sessions in the end, this forum is going to be on of the best yet!</string>

    <string-array name="materialType">
        <item>Type of material</item>
        <item>Video Lesson</item>
        <item>Practice</item>
        <item>Quiz</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="durationQuiz">
        <item>5</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>15</item>
        <item>20</item>
        <item>25</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>35</item>
        <item>40</item>
        <item>45</item>
        <item>50</item>
        <item>55</item>
        <item>60</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="questionType">
        <item>Multiple-question</item>
        <item>Fill-in-the-blank</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="doctor">"Doctors, also known as physicians, are licensed health professionals who maintain and restore human health through the practice of medicine. They examine patients, review their medical history, diagnose illnesses or injuries, administer treatment, and counsel patients on their health and well-being."</string>
    <string name="chemist">"A chemist is a scientist who performs research and experiments related to chemistry. They help to develop products like vaccinations and medications and analyze them to determine their composition, concentration and safety. They prepare technical reports to describe the methods and results of their research."</string>
    <string name="software_engineer">"A Software Engineer, or Software Development Engineer, is responsible for developing software programs or systems that align with user needs. Their duties include meeting with clients or business professionals to strategize ideas for beneficial software, coordinating with other IT professionals to design software and running tests to catch coding errors."</string>
    <string name="web_developer">"A web developer designs and programs websites, typically either on the front-end or back-end of production. Web developers code web pages and work on the interactivity and visual effects used in websites. They also analyze user needs, test the websites they develop and collect user feedback to improve the functionality of web pages."</string>
    <string name="computer_system_analyst">"A computer systems analyst helps companies improve their computer systems, resolve information technology-related issues, suggest enhancements and ensure their technology is up-to-date. A computer systems analyst might work on improving communication and security. They may also install new systems and programs and implement customized solutions based on the company's requirements."</string>
    <string name="cost_estimator">"A cost estimator analyzes data to determine the amount of money, materials, labor and time it takes to complete projects. Cost estimators try to ensure that projects stay within an established budget and that they're completed on time. They also manage bid pricing from vendors, prepare detailed cost analyses, discuss their estimates with team members and trade partners and establish and maintain relationships with vendors and subcontractors."</string>
    <string name="industrial_engineer">"An industrial engineer creates systems to help maximize the efficiency and productivity of manufacturing companies or service providers. They also try to reduce waste during the completion of projects and improve current processes. They may develop and implement quality control and cost-saving measures and standardize and optimize systems to distribute goods and services more efficiently."</string>
    <string name="civil_engineer">"A civil engineer works on construction projects such as roads or bridges. Their job involves designing, building and repairing large structures. They may specialize in a particular field, such as architectural, construction or transportation engineering."</string>
    <string name="mechanical_engineer">"A mechanical engineer works in a variety of industries and designs, creates and tests machines or mechanical devices. They can also repair machines like refrigerators, elevators and combustion engines. They play a crucial role in transforming an idea or plan into a product."</string>
    <string name="statistician">"A statistician collects and analyzes data and uses the results to help companies and organizations maximize their profits and minimize risk. They use the data they collect to inform business and investment decisions and identify trends in global markets and in different job fields. They help companies make reasonable conclusions using the results of their previous data analysis."</string>

    <string name="khazanah">"Offered by the Yayasan Khazanah foundation, this scholarship program is open to all Malaysian citizens. This government initiative provides fully-funded awards to students in fields like business, engineering, life sciences, and other fields necessary to Malaysia’s development. If you’re eligible, you receive complete financial support, covering fees, living costs, accommodation and more."</string>
    <string name="mybrainsc">"This is an initiative by the Malaysian Ministry of Education to raise a generation of young scientists and scholars. The program covers scholarship for Malaysian students at undergraduate and postgraduate levels enrolled in natural science programs. Scholarships for Malaysian students studying abroad are open for top globally ranked universities in the Australia, US, Canada, and UK. The award covers expenses including tuition fees, living costs, accommodation, and things like your flight tickets, visa-related fees and so on. After completing your studies you agree to return to Malaysia and work in a government-approved school or research institution."</string>
    <string name="bank_negara">"Bank Negara Malaysia offers full scholarships for Malaysian students abroad and at home, at pre-university, undergraduate and graduate levels. The award programs cover study in commerce, math and computer science fields."</string>
    <string name="jpa">"This government-provided scholarship funds foundational and undergraduate studies in Japan, Korea, France, and Germany. The fields funding is available to cover engineering, science, technology, and social sciences. This is a loan offered by the government to SPM students. You need to enrol in preparatory courses at a local school before attending a university in one of the 4 countries above."</string>
    <string name="fullbright">"This is a US-government program in partnership with 160 countries. Fullbright offers partial grants to Malaysian citizens for postgraduate study in the US. This means the grant supplements your personal funds and any existing scholarships or other funding you receive. The amount of the grant varies depending on the funding already available to you. So, this scholarship is a great option if you scored a partial scholarships from a home institution or the university you’ll be studying at."</string>
    <string name="british_council">"GREAT Scholarships is a partner program between the UK government and the British Council. A total of 30 scholarships across many different fields are on offer for postgraduate study. The scholarship amounts to £10,000 to cover tuition for a one-year postgraduate course at a UK university."</string>
</resources>